ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs
1983-1998
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4283 P
3.5 cubic feet
3.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
This is a collection of photographs from Buffalo Labour Studies, BLS Graduates, Career Development, Supervisory Studies, some action shots and miscellaneous ILR images as well as some from the jazz event for the 50th Anniversary reception.
6874704
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 04, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 04, 2019
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of photographs from Buffalo Labour Studies, BLS Graduates, Career Development, Supervisory Studies, some action shots and miscellaneous ILR images as well as some from the jazz event for the 50th Anniversary reception.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records /3071: ILR School Albany Extension Division Records /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4062m: ILR School Extension Division Albany Office Correspondence /4063: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4103: ILR School Extension Division Residential Study Institute Additional Records /4115: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4136m: ILR School Extension Division Additional Records /4233m: ILR School Western Regional Office Records /4233m: ILR School Western Regional Office Records /4283: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Audio-Visual Materials /4283 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Memorabilia /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4283/001: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Files /4283/001 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Audio-Visual Materials /4283/001 MB: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Memorabilia /4283/001 PUBS: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Publications /4283/001 (d): ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Lou Jean Fleron Born Digital Material /4283/002: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Files /4283/002 AV: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Audio-Visual Materials /4283/002 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Nellie Brown Photographs
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Western Regional Office--Photographs
6874704
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (1) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  24 photographs
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (2) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  28 photographs
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (4) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  30 photographs
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (6) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (6) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (7) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  25 photographs
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (8) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos (9) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  40 Photographs
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos 1983 (1) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Buffalo Labour Studies - Graduation Photos 1983 (2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  22 photographs
- BLS grad negatives - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  1 color photograph
- BLS grad photos 1988 (1) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- BLS Grad photos 1988 (2) (Box 1, Folder 14)
- BLS Grad Photos 1988 (3) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  18 photographs
- BLS Grad photos 1989 (1) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  29 photographs
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (2) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (3) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (4) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  20 photographs
- BLS grad photos 1989 (1) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (2) (Box 1, Folder 21)
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (3) (Box 1, Folder 22)
- BLS Grad Photos 1989 (4) (Box 1, Folder 23)
- BLS Grad photos (Buffalo State College) 1990 (1) (Box 1, Folder 24)
- BLS Grad Photos (Buffalo State College) 1990 (2) (Box 1, Folder 25)
- BLS Grad Photos (Buffalo State College) 1990 (3) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  15 photographs
- BLS Winter 1990 (1) (Box 1, Folder 27)
- BLS Winter 1990 (2) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  27 photographs
- BLS Winter 1990 (3) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  39 photographs
- BLS Grad Photos 1991 (1) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- BLS Grad Photos 1991 (2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  23 photographs
- BLS Grad Photos 1991 (3) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- BLS Grad Photos 1991 (4) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  40 photographs
- BLS Grad Photos 1993 (1) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- BLS Grad Photos 1993 (2) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- BLS Grad Photos 1993 (3) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  21 photographs
- GS grad photos BLS 1993 (1) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- GS grad photos BLS 1993 (2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Supervisory studies @ BSC 1980s (photos) (1) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Supervisory studies @ BSC 1980s (photos) (2) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Supervisory studies @ BSC 1980s (photos) (3) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Supervisory studies @ BSC 1980s (photos) (4) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  26 photographs
- Supervisory studies @ BSC 1980s (photos) (5) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  12 photographs
- Supervisory Studies, Grad & career development photos 1983 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  11 photographs
- Women's career development & supervisory studies grad 1984 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  14 photographs
- Supervisory studies grad 1989 Negs & photos (Box 2, Folder 17)
  31 photographs
- Supervisory studies grad 1996 (photos) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Local News articles related to Western NY Labour, 1967-1996: misc. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  25 p. text
- News stories - misc. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Overhead slides (presumably BLS program) - misc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  36 transparencies
- Timeline - misc. (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Timeline - misc. (2) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Labour Day Parade NY 1989 - Misc. (photos) (Box 3, Folder 4)
- BLS ceremony negs (Box 3, Folder 5)
- BLS negs ? (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Negs from BSC? - misc. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  1 photograph
- BLS photos & negs - misc. (Box 3, Folder 8)
- BLS photos - graduation or reunion? - misc. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  7 photographs
- BLS ceremony photos (Box 3, Folder 10)
- BLS ceremony photos (Box 3, Folder 11)
- BLS / Cornell Grads? - misc. (photos) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  4 photographs
- Action Shots - BLS - misc. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Cornell in Buffalo Workshop 1988 (negs & photos) - misc. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  38 photographs
- Industrial images for BLS brochure - misc. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  6 photographs
- Assorted photos, includes Labour Advisory Committee (Box 4, Folder 1)
  9 photographs
- Various industrial images - misc. (1) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  3 photographs
- Various industrial images - misc. (2) (Box 4, Folder 3)
- ILR images (1) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- ILR images (2) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  5 photographs
- ILR images (3) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- United Steel Workers and Strike images (Box 5, Folder 3)
  2 photographs
- Oversize prints - misc. (1) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  26 photo copies
- Oversize prints - misc. (2) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  30 photo copies
- Oversize prints - misc. (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Photos - misc. -(1) (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Photos - misc. (2) (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Cornell ILR Celebrating 50 years, program - misc. (Box 5, Folder 9)
- 50th Anniversary Program - misc. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Conference Photos (Box 6, Folder 19)
  pulled from /4283 box 123, f46 -- taken by Blue Photo & Video, Buffalo, NY
- Presentation slides - "Total Registered Births" (Box 6, Folder 18)
  pulled from /4283 box 140, f5
- Jody Miller Christmas Cards, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  pulled from /4283 box 125, f 16 (1989), f26 (1990)
- Laundry Strike Photo (Box 6, Folder 16)
  pulled from /4283 box 129/f48
- Buffalo Convention Center - photographs of a conference (Box 6, Folder 15)
  found in collection /4283, box 2, folder 32, removed and moved to this collection
- Panoramic Conference Picture (Box 6, Folder 20)
  pulled from /4283, box 143 (loose in box)
- DUN building Personnel/50th Anniversary. poster session 1996 - misc. (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 50th Anniversary Celebrations - photos 1996 - misc. (1) (Box 6, Folder 2)
- 50th Anniversary. celebrations - photos - 1996 (2) (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  32 photographs
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Photos - Rich Renaissance WR 50th Anniversary. Reception: 10-6-1997 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- BLS billboards 89-90 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- negs & photos grad 93 - misc. (Box 6, Folder 14)
- ILR Faculty Photo and Campus Photos (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 7, Folder 38)
  pulled from /4283 box 115
- Conference Photographs from Buffalo (Box 7, Folder 22)
  removed from /4283, box 38, folder 34
- Buffalo Conference photographs (Box 7, Folder 23)
  removed from /4283, box 48 (loose in box)
- Buffalo Conference Photographs (Box 7, Folder 24)
  removed from /4283, box 48, folder 37
- Buffalo Labor Studies Program, Class of 1977 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  removed from /4283, box 48, folder 21
- Conference Photos (Box 7, Folder 26)
  pulled from /4283 b82/f13
- Photo of an air vent (Box 7, Folder 27)
  pulled from /4283 - box 54/f2
- Misc. Photos (Box 7, Folder 28)
  pulled from /4283 box 85 (loose in box)
- Conference Photo (Box 7, Folder 29)
  pulled from /4283 box 94/f25
- Christmas Party Photo (Box 7, Folder 30)
  pulled from bx 115/ff3
- Award Ceremony (?) at Cornell University (Box 7, Folder 31)
  pulled from bx 117/ff12
- Jeanette - Miscellaneous Photos: 1953-1970 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- 'Ethnic' Photographs (Box 7, Folder 33)
  pulled from box 115
- Misc. Photos (Box 7, Folder 34)
  pulled from /4283 bx 115
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 7, Folder 35)
  pulled from /4238, box 115
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Miscellaneous Photos (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  31 slides
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  35 slides
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  24 slides
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  27 slides
- Institute for Industry Studies (NYSSILR) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  22 slides
- Unlabeled slides (Box 7, Folder 7)
  4 slides
- Niagara: Attracting the World - Book project (Box 7, Folder 8)
  21 photographs; 3 slides
- Niagara: Attracting the World - Book project (Box 7, Folder 9)
  38 slides; 1 photo copy; negs
- EEOC / Cornell - Mediation Training: 3/10-11/1998 at Western Region (Box 7, Folder 10)
- EEOC / Cornell - Mediation Training: 3/10-11/1998 at Western Region (Box 7, Folder 11)
- WR - 50th Anniversary. Jazz Event 9-7-1997; Reception 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  31 photographs -- Photos grouped so kept together in folders
- WR 50th Anniversary. Jazz Event - 9-7-1997; Reception - 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  18 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. groupings
- WR 50th Anniversary. Jazz Event: 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  29 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. groupings
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  24 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. groupings
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  21 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. groupings
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  37 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. groupings
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  14 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. order
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  30 photographs -- Photos kept in orig. grouping
- WR 50th Anniversary.: Jazz Event -- 9-7-1997; Reception -- 10-6-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)